hey guys I saw this thing from Iota
Academy it says I want to believe and it
shows this really interesting equation
let's verify that this thing is true so
first step let's subtract one from both
sides on the left hand side we just have
this thing minus one and on the right
hand side we just have this fraction I
don't like fractions so I'm going to
multiply both sides by this denominator
these two things are going to cancel out
which leaves me with just pi to the E
minus one and on the left hand side we
could just bring this stuff down now
let's foil root pi to the E times root
pi to the E is just pi to the E root pi
to the E times negative 1 is negative
root pi to the e one times root pi to
the U is root pi to the E and 1 times
negative 1 is equal to negative 1. now
we can bring down the right hand side
these two middle terms are the same so
they're going to cancel each other out
or just left with pi to the E minus 1
equals pi to the E minus 1. so this up
here is a true statement how exciting